{
    "subject": "resource/Zoya_Ivanova",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/description",
    "object": "Athletics (sport)competitor",
    "human_readable": "Zoya Ivanova is an athletics competitor.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9639790058135986,
            "question": "Is Zoya Ivanova a professional athlete?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9569579362869263,
            "question": "What kind of competitor is Zoya Ivanova?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9550031423568726,
            "question": "What sport does Zoya Ivanova compete in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9468047022819519,
            "question": "Who are some of Zoya Ivanova's competitors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.756152868270874,
            "question": "What are Zoya Ivanova's future goals in athletics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.579828143119812,
            "question": "What are some of Zoya Ivanova's accomplishments?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5387957692146301,
            "question": "Has Zoya Ivanova won any medals?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4671359062194824,
            "question": "Does Zoya Ivanova have any role models?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4157409071922302,
            "question": "What is Zoya Ivanova's training regimen like?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31962528824806213,
            "question": "Where does Zoya Ivanova train?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Zoya Ivanova is an athletics competitor.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1320_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Zoya Ivanova's training regimen like?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1320_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Zoya Ivanova have any role models?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1320_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Zoya Ivanova won any medals?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1320_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1320_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1320_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1320_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1320_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1320_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1320_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1320_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1320_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1320_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1320_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Zoya Ivanova competes in marathon events, which falls under the category of athletics. Therefore, the statement \"Zoya Ivanova is an athletics competitor\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}